https://www.addressstamp.com/privacy.php

Our Youtube Channel with How To Order Videos
How to send us filesArtwork Clean-up / Conversion FeesGeneral Artwork GuidelinesShipping Charges and Delivery TimesRush Policy & PricingTrademarks and CopyrightsPrivacy PolicyPartner LinksHoliday ScheduleContact UsHours of Operation / Live Help
Manufacturer Catalogs
Our Popular Office Stamp Catalog2000 PlusIdeal / UltimarkMaxStamp (formerly Maxum Plus)Shiny / PSIShinyTrodat StandardTrodat ExpandedTrodat and IdealTrodat Cross Reference ChartRubber Stamp Catalog
General Information
Payment InformationCredit ApplicationPurchase Order InformationGovernment Contracting OpportunitiesGeneral Terms and InformationTerms of Use
Also Visit Us at
PromoteSource.com - Advertising Specialties
iTuit.com - Custom Imprinted Wooden Nickels and Plastic Tokens
Search
We Accept
Verifications
Online Payments
Members of
Our Privacy Policy
At PromoteSource, the parent company of AddressStamp.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect
about you to provide a more personalized business relationship. Please read on for more details
about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? And how do we use it?
When you order from us online for the first time, we need to know your name, e-mail address,
mailing address, firm name, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and
fulfill your order and notify you of your order status.
When you inquire about our potential services to you, we ask for your name, mailing address, and
e-mail address so we can send you the appropriate samples and/or information to fulfill your request.
We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to formulate our recommendations
about the products and merchandise that may interest you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns
and site usage to assist in the design and layout of our website. We can also use the information
collected to notify you about important changes to the web site, new services, and special offers
we think you'll find valuable.
Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. We may also use your IP
address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site.
How does PromoteSource protect customer information?
All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
We also follow these additional principles of Privacy:
1. We do not use any information about pages you visit on our site or the Web, and we do not
give it out to others.
2. We do not give out your telephone number, credit card information, or screen names, unless
you authorize us to do so. And we give you the opportunity to correct your personal contact and
billing information at any time.
3. We may use information about the types of products you buy from us to make other marketing
offers to you, unless you tell us not to. We do not give out this purchase data to others.
4. We give you choices about how PromoteSource uses your personal information.
5. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access
in order to safeguard your personal information.
6. We keep you informed on this page about our privacy policies.
Will PromoteSource disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
PromoteSource does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Also,
PromoteSource does not provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns,
and related site information to any third-party. PromoteSource may release account information when
we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii)
enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or
safety of PromoteSource, our users, or others.
How does PromoteSource allow customers to update or change the information it collects?
You may update or change information related to your PromoteSource account by emailing us.
In Summary
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use information collected on our site to make your
visit to PromoteSource as safe as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do
not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Your Consent
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by PromoteSource.
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the site
means that you agree with the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our
privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what
information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Links
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the
information under our control. However, any links from this website are not under our control and
therefore, not governed by our privacy policies. PromoteSource is not responsible for those websites.
Tell us what you think
PromoteSource welcomes your questions and comments about privacy.
Continue
Shopping Cart
0 items
Bestsellers
01.Maxum Plus 3 Line Self Inking Stamp MX 1Qty of 202.Colop Green Line Printer Self Inking Stamp 20GL Qty of 203.Maxum Plus 4 Line Self Inking Stamp MX 1Qty of 204.Colop Green Line Printer Self Inking Stamp 30GL Qty of 205.2000 Plus Printer R17 Self Inking Round Stamp
Friday December 11, 2020
AddressStamp.com by PromoteSource®
Please note: Charges will appear on your credit card statement as PromoteSource.
Please make all checks or money orders payable to PromoteSource.
800 Village Square Crossing • Suite 325 • Palm Beach Gardens, Florida 33410
Please Reply To: Post Office Box 32824 • Palm Beach Gardens, Florida 33420
Direct Telephone (561) 203-8869
Toll Free (888) 406-8950 • Toll Free Fax (888) 406-8951
PromoteSource® is a registered trademark of Midaco Group, LLC
This website is owned and operated by Midaco Group, LLC, a Florida Limited Liability Company, dba PromoteSource.
Content Copyright © 2003 - 2020, Midaco Group, LLC dba PromoteSource®. All rights reserved.
Content licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works 3.0 United States License.
